This is Hamaya Hiromasa.  I run a company.   It's
Hamaya Nao.  I work as a professional caddy.
[Music]
Well, to be honest about my brother's job, it's
not a very stable profession, and we
receive incentives from the prize money of the athletes, so depending on the athletes
' performance, the incentive can be
zero. And since I have my brother as an employee, I felt that I had to
protect him somehow, so I got to know the
person in charge now
, and they have given me
various advice on how to proceed given the current situation and on life planning, and the
company has taken out insurance to
protect my brother as well
.  I
think having insurance is what allows me to connect with my pet carrier freely and happily right now
.  I don't usually say it out loud, but he's an older
brother I truly respect.
Make sure choices in your life.